

Geetanjali Negi

House -9, Gali-1, Nirankari colony

Delhi, 110009

Phone: 9372560455

Email: geetanjalidumik02937@gmail.com

Objective

With curiosity of exploring emerging trends and phenomena shaping our society and a commitment to rigorous research methodologies and interdisciplinary approaches, I aim to contribute meaningful insights to the field while learning and growing at the same time.

Experience

Himachal Pradesh University / Guest Faculty

NOV 2021 - DEC 2021

Enabled learning of students pursuing masters in social work and worked on the development of teaching and study material.

International Socio-economics Laboratory (ISL) / Principal Investigator JUNE 2021 - AUG 2021

Worked closely as a research guide to the students pursuing research projects. Provided support and guidance on the designing of the research project.

Education

Department of Social Work, University of Delhi / Mphil

JAN 2022 - JAN 2024, DELHI

Holds Junior Research Fellowship (JRF). Pursued research on the topic "A study about the experiences of families of capital defendants".

Tata Institute of Social Sciences (TISS) / Masters in Social Work

MARCH 2018 - MARCH 2020, MUMBAI

Has field work experience of working with organizations like IRHDP, PRAYAS and Mahamanav Baba Amte Seva Sanstha. As a part of course, successfully pursued research on the topic "Victimization survey of Solan in Himachal Pradesh".

Department of Biochemistry, Panjab University / B.sc

JAN 2014 - JAN 2017, CHANDIGARH

Took up the responsibility of Literary Incharge of the Department.

Strengths and Skills	Community mapping, Project management, casework, and group work methods, active listening, observation skills, ability to work in a group as well as independently, and ability to hold multiple perspectives.
_	
Languages Known	English and Hindi.